<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Amazon on AshTop5Tech</title>
    <link>https://ashyadav.github.com/ashtech/tags/amazon/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Amazon on AshTop5Tech</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-EN</language>
    <copyright>All rights reserved - 2016</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 May 2016 21:52:37 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://ashyadav.github.com/ashtech/tags/amazon/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>AshTop5Tech #6 - Parsey McParseface</title>
      <link>https://ashyadav.github.com/ashtech/post/techsix/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2016 21:52:37 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashyadav.github.com/ashtech/post/techsix/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;SWIFT, Eye Computer, VIV, Bitcoin, Parsey McPareface&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;another-swift-attack:b2b61fc48fbebe9d570f15a2a61d96bd&#34;&gt;Another SWIFT Attack&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://goo.gl/n3pPaH&#34;&gt;http://goo.gl/n3pPaH&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The SWIFT interbank network that  handles money transfers between bank has seen its second major hack attack.  SWIFT is the primary way banks move billions of dollars to other banks daily. The hack spreads malware using a pdf reader software and bears code signatures similar to the Sony hack and the recent attack on the Bangladesh Central Bank. So if you work at a bank and are reading swift message via a pdf reader make sure its not infected and stay vigilant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;a-computer-in-your-eye:b2b61fc48fbebe9d570f15a2a61d96bd&#34;&gt;A computer in your eye&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(&lt;a href=&#34;http://goo.gl/5ZHy4G&#34;&gt;http://goo.gl/5ZHy4G&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Google glass was a stepping stone to the next gen devices google is dreaming up. Not content with the public rejection of google glass the company continues to push the envelope on a wearable computer. It latest vision via a patent filing is to implant one directly into your eyeball.  Once injected the device would be powered by an energy harvesting antenna. The device can transmit  signals like GPS, NFC, LTE. Will it be able to interact with the optic nerve and beam signals directly to the neo cortex is still unknown.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;viv-conversation-as-a-platform-caap:b2b61fc48fbebe9d570f15a2a61d96bd&#34;&gt;Viv - Conversation as a platform CAAP&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(&lt;a href=&#34;http://goo.gl/wDLp5H&#34;&gt;http://goo.gl/wDLp5H&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A new conversational bot named Viv was unveiled  last week by the creators of Siri. Viv promises to be the bridge between the apps on your device. You could ask Viv to order some flowers for mom or the temperature at the golden gate bridge at 7pm. You could even ask it to send some money to your friends. The AI assistant would be social graph and service aware to make the autonomous decisions for you. Will Viv be a radical change or just another bot that is gobbled up  by Siri, Cortana or Ok Google&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;will-the-real-satoshi-nakamato-please-stand-up:b2b61fc48fbebe9d570f15a2a61d96bd&#34;&gt;Will the real Satoshi Nakamato please stand up &amp;hellip;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(&lt;a href=&#34;https://goo.gl/kCy4Vh&#34;&gt;https://goo.gl/kCy4Vh&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The elusive founder of bitcoin  was found and lost again. Australian Craig Steve Wright was briefly unmasked as the infamous  Satoshi Nakamoto, founder of bitcoin. Several clues including a PGP pubic key, blog posts and the mysterious &amp;ldquo;Tulip Trust&amp;rdquo; .  Clues that surfaced after the release of the Wired story point an elaborate hoax that Wright may be propagating. So once more Nakamoto-san slips back into matrix..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cause I&amp;rsquo;m Slim Shady, yes I&amp;rsquo;m the real Shady
All you other Slim Shadys are just imitating
So won&amp;rsquo;t the real Slim Shady please stand up,
Please stand up, please stand up?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;parsey-mcparseface:b2b61fc48fbebe9d570f15a2a61d96bd&#34;&gt;Parsey McParseface&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(&lt;a href=&#34;http://goo.gl/dxd3ih&#34;&gt;http://goo.gl/dxd3ih&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Google this week open sourced its natural language parser. This will enable smarter applications that one can communicate with using natural language. This should make chatbots smarter. The parser SyntaxNet is a Neural network built on googles macdhine learning framework Tensor Flow.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>