<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ashtech</title>
    <link>https://ashyadav.github.io/ashtech/tags/apple/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content on ashtech</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-EN</language>
    <copyright>All rights reserved - 2016</copyright>
    <atom:link href="https://ashyadav.github.io/ashtech/tags/apple/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>AshTech #9 Apple Airpods</title>
      <link>https://ashyadav.github.io/ashtech/post/airpods/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 21:18:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ashyadav.github.io/ashtech/post/airpods/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After whats seemed like an eternity, Apple has delivered on their promise of Airpods for christmas. Apple hit some unexplained delivery delays on these headphones after it courageously removed the headphone jack on the iphone7.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
Well they have finally arrived in mailboxes and apple stores. In true fashion apple under promised and over delivered by delivering my headphones 2 days ahead of time on launch day&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My First impressions of using them for the last few days has been great so far. The airpods paired as soon I opened up the case ( and charger ) thanks to the new W1 chip. They fit snugly in my ears and seem very hard to drop. They sound great to my ears.  Much better than the wired ones. I have noticed that the stereo separation is much better as I picked up sounds that I have not previously. My standard testing tracks of Pink Floyd, Eagles and the beats radio station were my initial testbed. I have listened to multiple podcasts without any drops outs while roaming thru the house and long dog walks.  I  watched a  Netflix shows with no lag on my iPad Pro. Thanks to the apple magic sauce they show up magically on  my apple watch, ipads, and computer via icloud.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are some more that provide more details  on one of my favorite gadgets of the year.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reviews&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://goo.gl/2PhLs1&#34;&gt;9to5mac review &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://goo.gl/4qLGms&#34;&gt;The Verge review&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://goo.gl/YGUuzd&#34;&gt;imore review&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>